[
 {
	"QuestionID" : 0,
	"Question" : "What is 8 + 6 X 7?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eight plus six times seven?", 
	"Answer" : 50,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 98,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added eight and six before you multiplied by seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 X 7 before adding 8 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 7 = 42; Now we have 8 + 42 = 50"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 1,
	"Question" : "What is (7 + 6) X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (seven plus six) times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 117,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and seventeen.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 61,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied six and nine before you added seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 7 + 6 before multiplying 9 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 + 6 = 13; Now we have 13 X 9 = 117"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 2,
	"Question" : "What is 9 + 0 X 8?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine plus zero times eight?", 
	"Answer" : 9,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is nine.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 72,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added nine and zero before you multiplied by eight.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 0 X 8 before adding 9 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 X 8 = 0; Now we have 9 + 0 = 9"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 3,
	"Question" : "What is 3 X (9 + 8)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three times (nine plus eight?)", 
	"Answer" : 51,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-one.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 35,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied three and nine before you added eight.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 8 + 9 before multiplying 3 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 + 8 = 17; Now we have 3 X 17 = 51"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 4,
	"Question" : "What is 4 + 4 X 7?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four plus four times seven?", 
	"Answer" : 32,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-two.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 56,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added four and four before you multiplied by seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 4 X 7 before adding 4 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "4 X 7 = 28; Now we have 4 + 28 = 32"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 5,
	"Question" : "What is (3 + 0) X 5?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (three plus zero) times five?", 
	"Answer" : 15,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifteen.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 3,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied zero and five before you added three.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 3 + 0 before multiplying 5 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 0 = 3; Now we have 3 X 5 = 15"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 6,
	"Question" : "What is 7 + 5 X 8?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven plus five times eight?", 
	"Answer" : 47,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-seven.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 96,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added seven and five before you multiplied by eight.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 5 X 8 before adding 7 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 X 8 = 40; Now we have 7 + 40 = 47"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 7,
	"Question" : "What is (5 + 4) X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (five plus four) times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 0,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is zero.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 5,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied four and zero before you added five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 5 + 4 before multiplying 0 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 + 4 = 9; Now we have 9 X 0 = 0"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 8,
	"Question" : "What is 8 + 3 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eight plus three times one?", 
	"Answer" : 11,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eleven.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 11,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added eight and three before you multiplied by one.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 3 X 1 before adding 8 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 X 1 = 3; Now we have 8 + 3 = 11"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 9,
	"Question" : "What is 1 X (3 + 3)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one times (three plus three?)", 
	"Answer" : 6,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is six.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 6,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied one and three before you added three.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 3 + 3 before multiplying 1 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 3 = 6; Now we have 1 X 6 = 6"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 10,
	"Question" : "What is 5 + 6 X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five plus six times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 59,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-nine.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 99,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added five and six before you multiplied by nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 X 9 before adding 5 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 9 = 54; Now we have 5 + 54 = 59"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 11,
	"Question" : "What is (2 + 2) X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (two plus two) times one?", 
	"Answer" : 4,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 4,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied two and one before you added two.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 + 2 before multiplying 1 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 + 2 = 4; Now we have 4 X 1 = 4"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 12,
	"Question" : "What is 4 + 2 X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four plus two times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 22,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-two.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 54,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added four and two before you multiplied by nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 2 X 9 before adding 4 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 X 9 = 18; Now we have 4 + 18 = 22"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 13,
	"Question" : "What is 6 X (7 + 5)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is six times (seven plus five?)", 
	"Answer" : 72,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventy-two.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 47,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied six and seven before you added five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 5 + 7 before multiplying 6 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 + 5 = 12; Now we have 6 X 12 = 72"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 14,
	"Question" : "What is 8 + 2 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eight plus two times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 8,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eight.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 0,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added eight and two before you multiplied by zero.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 2 X 0 before adding 8 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 X 0 = 0; Now we have 8 + 0 = 8"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 15,
	"Question" : "What is 5 X (5 + 5)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five times (five plus five?)", 
	"Answer" : 50,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 30,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied five and five before you added five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 5 + 5 before multiplying 5 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 + 5 = 10; Now we have 5 X 10 = 50"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 16,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 9 X 8?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus nine times eight?", 
	"Answer" : 73,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventy-three.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 80,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added one and nine before you multiplied by eight.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 9 X 8 before adding 1 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 X 8 = 72; Now we have 1 + 72 = 73"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 17,
	"Question" : "What is 1 X (5 + 3)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one times (five plus three?)", 
	"Answer" : 8,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eight.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 8,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied one and five before you added three.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 3 + 5 before multiplying 1 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 + 3 = 8; Now we have 1 X 8 = 8"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 18,
	"Question" : "What is 2 + 1 X 8?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is two plus one times eight?", 
	"Answer" : 10,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is ten.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 24,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added two and one before you multiplied by eight.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 1 X 8 before adding 2 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 X 8 = 8; Now we have 2 + 8 = 10"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 19,
	"Question" : "What is 1 X (5 + 7)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one times (five plus seven?)", 
	"Answer" : 12,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twelve.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 12,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied one and five before you added seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 7 + 5 before multiplying 1 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 + 7 = 12; Now we have 1 X 12 = 12"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 20,
	"Question" : "What is 3 + 1 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three plus one times two?", 
	"Answer" : 5,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is five.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 8,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added three and one before you multiplied by two.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 1 X 2 before adding 3 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 X 2 = 2; Now we have 3 + 2 = 5"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 21,
	"Question" : "What is (4 + 8) X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (four plus eight) times four?", 
	"Answer" : 48,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-eight.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 36,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied eight and four before you added four.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 4 + 8 before multiplying 4 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "4 + 8 = 12; Now we have 12 X 4 = 48"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 22,
	"Question" : "What is 5 + 3 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five plus three times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 5,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is five.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 0,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added five and three before you multiplied by zero.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 3 X 0 before adding 5 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 X 0 = 0; Now we have 5 + 0 = 5"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 23,
	"Question" : "What is 6 X (1 + 3)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is six times (one plus three?)", 
	"Answer" : 24,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 9,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied six and one before you added three.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 3 + 1 before multiplying 6 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 3 = 4; Now we have 6 X 4 = 24"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 24,
	"Question" : "What is 8 + 9 X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eight plus nine times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 89,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eighty-nine.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 153,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added eight and nine before you multiplied by nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 9 X 9 before adding 8 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 X 9 = 81; Now we have 8 + 81 = 89"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 25,
	"Question" : "What is (5 + 4) X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (five plus four) times three?", 
	"Answer" : 27,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-seven.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 17,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied four and three before you added five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 5 + 4 before multiplying 3 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 + 4 = 9; Now we have 9 X 3 = 27"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 26,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 2 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus two times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 1,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 0,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added one and two before you multiplied by zero.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 2 X 0 before adding 1 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 X 0 = 0; Now we have 1 + 0 = 1"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 27,
	"Question" : "What is 6 X (9 + 4)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is six times (nine plus four?)", 
	"Answer" : 78,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventy-eight.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 58,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied six and nine before you added four.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 4 + 9 before multiplying 6 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 + 4 = 13; Now we have 6 X 13 = 78"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 28,
	"Question" : "What is 2 + 7 X 7?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is two plus seven times seven?", 
	"Answer" : 51,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-one.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 63,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added two and seven before you multiplied by seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 7 X 7 before adding 2 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 X 7 = 49; Now we have 2 + 49 = 51"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 29,
	"Question" : "What is (2 + 2) X 7?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (two plus two) times seven?", 
	"Answer" : 28,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-eight.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 16,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied two and seven before you added two.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 + 2 before multiplying 7 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 + 2 = 4; Now we have 4 X 7 = 28"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 30,
	"Question" : "What is 5 + 7 X 6?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five plus seven times six?", 
	"Answer" : 47,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-seven.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 72,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added five and seven before you multiplied by six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 7 X 6 before adding 5 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 X 6 = 42; Now we have 5 + 42 = 47"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 31,
	"Question" : "What is 3 X (1 + 3)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three times (one plus three?)", 
	"Answer" : 12,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twelve.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 6,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied three and one before you added three.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 3 + 1 before multiplying 3 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 3 = 4; Now we have 3 X 4 = 12"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 32,
	"Question" : "What is 8 + 9 X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eight plus nine times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 89,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eighty-nine.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 153,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added eight and nine before you multiplied by nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 9 X 9 before adding 8 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 X 9 = 81; Now we have 8 + 81 = 89"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 33,
	"Question" : "What is 7 X (1 + 7)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven times (one plus seven?)", 
	"Answer" : 56,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-six.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 14,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied seven and one before you added seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 7 + 1 before multiplying 7 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 7 = 8; Now we have 7 X 8 = 56"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 34,
	"Question" : "What is 6 + 4 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is six plus four times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 6,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is six.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 0,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added six and four before you multiplied by zero.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 4 X 0 before adding 6 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "4 X 0 = 0; Now we have 6 + 0 = 6"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 35,
	"Question" : "What is 1 X (3 + 6)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one times (three plus six?)", 
	"Answer" : 9,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is nine.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 9,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied one and three before you added six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 6 + 3 before multiplying 1 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 6 = 9; Now we have 1 X 9 = 9"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 36,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 6 X 5?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus six times five?", 
	"Answer" : 31,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-one.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 35,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added one and six before you multiplied by five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 X 5 before adding 1 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 5 = 30; Now we have 1 + 30 = 31"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 37,
	"Question" : "What is (3 + 4) X 6?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (three plus four) times six?", 
	"Answer" : 42,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-two.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 27,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied four and six before you added three.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 3 + 4 before multiplying 6 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 4 = 7; Now we have 7 X 6 = 42"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 38,
	"Question" : "What is 4 + 3 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four plus three times four?", 
	"Answer" : 16,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixteen.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 28,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added four and three before you multiplied by four.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 3 X 4 before adding 4 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 X 4 = 12; Now we have 4 + 12 = 16"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 39,
	"Question" : "What is (8 + 0) X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (eight plus zero) times four?", 
	"Answer" : 32,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-two.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 8,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied zero and four before you added eight.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 8 + 0 before multiplying 4 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 + 0 = 8; Now we have 8 X 4 = 32"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 40,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 7 X 6?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus seven times six?", 
	"Answer" : 43,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-three.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 48,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added one and seven before you multiplied by six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 7 X 6 before adding 1 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 X 6 = 42; Now we have 1 + 42 = 43"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 41,
	"Question" : "What is 8 X (9 + 5)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eight times (nine plus five?)", 
	"Answer" : 112,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and twelve.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 77,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied eight and nine before you added five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 5 + 9 before multiplying 8 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 + 5 = 14; Now we have 8 X 14 = 112"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 42,
	"Question" : "What is 5 + 2 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five plus two times two?", 
	"Answer" : 9,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is nine.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 14,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added five and two before you multiplied by two.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 2 X 2 before adding 5 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 X 2 = 4; Now we have 5 + 4 = 9"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 43,
	"Question" : "What is (4 + 4) X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (four plus four) times one?", 
	"Answer" : 8,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eight.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 8,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied four and one before you added four.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 4 + 4 before multiplying 1 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "4 + 4 = 8; Now we have 8 X 1 = 8"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 44,
	"Question" : "What is 8 + 6 X 6?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eight plus six times six?", 
	"Answer" : 44,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 84,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added eight and six before you multiplied by six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 X 6 before adding 8 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 6 = 36; Now we have 8 + 36 = 44"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 45,
	"Question" : "What is 9 X (5 + 4)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine times (five plus four?)", 
	"Answer" : 81,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eighty-one.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 49,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied nine and five before you added four.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 4 + 5 before multiplying 9 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 + 4 = 9; Now we have 9 X 9 = 81"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 46,
	"Question" : "What is 5 + 6 X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five plus six times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 59,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-nine.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 99,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added five and six before you multiplied by nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 X 9 before adding 5 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 9 = 54; Now we have 5 + 54 = 59"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 47,
	"Question" : "What is 6 X (1 + 0)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is six times (one plus zero?)", 
	"Answer" : 6,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is six.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 6,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied six and one before you added zero.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 + 1 before multiplying 6 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 0 = 1; Now we have 6 X 1 = 6"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 48,
	"Question" : "What is 3 + 2 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three plus two times two?", 
	"Answer" : 7,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seven.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 10,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added three and two before you multiplied by two.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 2 X 2 before adding 3 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 X 2 = 4; Now we have 3 + 4 = 7"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 49,
	"Question" : "What is 7 X (7 + 9)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven times (seven plus nine?)", 
	"Answer" : 112,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and twelve.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 58,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied seven and seven before you added nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 9 + 7 before multiplying 7 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 + 9 = 16; Now we have 7 X 16 = 112"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 50,
	"Question" : "What is 2 + 8 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is two plus eight times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 2,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is two.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 0,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added two and eight before you multiplied by zero.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 8 X 0 before adding 2 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 X 0 = 0; Now we have 2 + 0 = 2"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 51,
	"Question" : "What is 9 X (5 + 5)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine times (five plus five?)", 
	"Answer" : 90,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is ninety.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 50,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied nine and five before you added five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 5 + 5 before multiplying 9 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 + 5 = 10; Now we have 9 X 10 = 90"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 52,
	"Question" : "What is 2 + 9 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is two plus nine times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 2,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is two.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 0,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added two and nine before you multiplied by zero.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 9 X 0 before adding 2 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 X 0 = 0; Now we have 2 + 0 = 2"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 53,
	"Question" : "What is (2 + 6) X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (two plus six) times one?", 
	"Answer" : 8,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eight.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 8,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied six and one before you added two.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 + 6 before multiplying 1 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 + 6 = 8; Now we have 8 X 1 = 8"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 54,
	"Question" : "What is 5 + 5 X 8?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five plus five times eight?", 
	"Answer" : 45,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-five.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 80,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added five and five before you multiplied by eight.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 5 X 8 before adding 5 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 X 8 = 40; Now we have 5 + 40 = 45"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 55,
	"Question" : "What is (2 + 2) X 8?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (two plus two) times eight?", 
	"Answer" : 32,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-two.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 18,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied two and eight before you added two.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 + 2 before multiplying 8 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 + 2 = 4; Now we have 4 X 8 = 32"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 56,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 7 X 5?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus seven times five?", 
	"Answer" : 36,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-six.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 40,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added one and seven before you multiplied by five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 7 X 5 before adding 1 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 X 5 = 35; Now we have 1 + 35 = 36"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 57,
	"Question" : "What is 5 X (7 + 6)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five times (seven plus six?)", 
	"Answer" : 65,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixty-five.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 41,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied five and seven before you added six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 6 + 7 before multiplying 5 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 + 6 = 13; Now we have 5 X 13 = 65"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 58,
	"Question" : "What is 4 + 8 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four plus eight times two?", 
	"Answer" : 20,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 24,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added four and eight before you multiplied by two.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 8 X 2 before adding 4 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 X 2 = 16; Now we have 4 + 16 = 20"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 59,
	"Question" : "What is 8 X (5 + 8)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eight times (five plus eight?)", 
	"Answer" : 104,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 48,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied eight and five before you added eight.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 8 + 5 before multiplying 8 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 + 8 = 13; Now we have 8 X 13 = 104"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 60,
	"Question" : "What is 3 + 6 X 6?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three plus six times six?", 
	"Answer" : 39,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-nine.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 54,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added three and six before you multiplied by six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 X 6 before adding 3 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 6 = 36; Now we have 3 + 36 = 39"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 61,
	"Question" : "What is (4 + 0) X 8?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (four plus zero) times eight?", 
	"Answer" : 32,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-two.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 4,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied zero and eight before you added four.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 4 + 0 before multiplying 8 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "4 + 0 = 4; Now we have 4 X 8 = 32"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 62,
	"Question" : "What is 7 + 8 X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven plus eight times three?", 
	"Answer" : 31,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-one.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 45,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added seven and eight before you multiplied by three.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 8 X 3 before adding 7 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 X 3 = 24; Now we have 7 + 24 = 31"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 63,
	"Question" : "What is (8 + 8) X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (eight plus eight) times two?", 
	"Answer" : 32,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-two.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 24,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied eight and two before you added eight.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 8 + 8 before multiplying 2 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 + 8 = 16; Now we have 16 X 2 = 32"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 64,
	"Question" : "What is 4 + 0 X 5?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four plus zero times five?", 
	"Answer" : 4,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 20,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added four and zero before you multiplied by five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 0 X 5 before adding 4 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 X 5 = 0; Now we have 4 + 0 = 4"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 65,
	"Question" : "What is 3 X (1 + 7)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three times (one plus seven?)", 
	"Answer" : 24,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 10,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied three and one before you added seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 7 + 1 before multiplying 3 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 7 = 8; Now we have 3 X 8 = 24"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 66,
	"Question" : "What is 4 + 4 X 5?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four plus four times five?", 
	"Answer" : 24,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 40,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added four and four before you multiplied by five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 4 X 5 before adding 4 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "4 X 5 = 20; Now we have 4 + 20 = 24"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 67,
	"Question" : "What is 1 X (1 + 9)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one times (one plus nine?)", 
	"Answer" : 10,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is ten.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 10,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied one and one before you added nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 9 + 1 before multiplying 1 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 9 = 10; Now we have 1 X 10 = 10"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 68,
	"Question" : "What is 6 + 0 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is six plus zero times four?", 
	"Answer" : 6,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is six.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 24,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added six and zero before you multiplied by four.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 0 X 4 before adding 6 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 X 4 = 0; Now we have 6 + 0 = 6"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 69,
	"Question" : "What is 9 X (1 + 9)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine times (one plus nine?)", 
	"Answer" : 90,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is ninety.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 18,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied nine and one before you added nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 9 + 1 before multiplying 9 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 9 = 10; Now we have 9 X 10 = 90"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 70,
	"Question" : "What is 4 + 0 X 7?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four plus zero times seven?", 
	"Answer" : 4,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 28,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added four and zero before you multiplied by seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 0 X 7 before adding 4 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 X 7 = 0; Now we have 4 + 0 = 4"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 71,
	"Question" : "What is 9 X (3 + 5)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine times (three plus five?)", 
	"Answer" : 72,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventy-two.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 32,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied nine and three before you added five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 5 + 3 before multiplying 9 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 5 = 8; Now we have 9 X 8 = 72"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 72,
	"Question" : "What is 4 + 5 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four plus five times one?", 
	"Answer" : 9,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is nine.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 9,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added four and five before you multiplied by one.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 5 X 1 before adding 4 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 X 1 = 5; Now we have 4 + 5 = 9"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 73,
	"Question" : "What is (5 + 6) X 5?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (five plus six) times five?", 
	"Answer" : 55,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-five.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 35,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied six and five before you added five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 5 + 6 before multiplying 5 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 + 6 = 11; Now we have 11 X 5 = 55"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 74,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 3 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus three times one?", 
	"Answer" : 4,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 4,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added one and three before you multiplied by one.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 3 X 1 before adding 1 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 X 1 = 3; Now we have 1 + 3 = 4"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 75,
	"Question" : "What is 7 X (3 + 0)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven times (three plus zero?)", 
	"Answer" : 21,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-one.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 21,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied seven and three before you added zero.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 + 3 before multiplying 7 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 0 = 3; Now we have 7 X 3 = 21"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 76,
	"Question" : "What is 8 + 8 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eight plus eight times two?", 
	"Answer" : 24,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 32,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added eight and eight before you multiplied by two.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 8 X 2 before adding 8 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 X 2 = 16; Now we have 8 + 16 = 24"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 77,
	"Question" : "What is (5 + 8) X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (five plus eight) times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 117,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and seventeen.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 77,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied eight and nine before you added five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 5 + 8 before multiplying 9 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 + 8 = 13; Now we have 13 X 9 = 117"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 78,
	"Question" : "What is 9 + 6 X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine plus six times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 63,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixty-three.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 135,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added nine and six before you multiplied by nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 X 9 before adding 9 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 9 = 54; Now we have 9 + 54 = 63"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 79,
	"Question" : "What is (9 + 0) X 8?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (nine plus zero) times eight?", 
	"Answer" : 72,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventy-two.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 9,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied zero and eight before you added nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 9 + 0 before multiplying 8 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 + 0 = 9; Now we have 9 X 8 = 72"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 80,
	"Question" : "What is 6 + 9 X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is six plus nine times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 87,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eighty-seven.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 135,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added six and nine before you multiplied by nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 9 X 9 before adding 6 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 X 9 = 81; Now we have 6 + 81 = 87"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 81,
	"Question" : "What is 7 X (3 + 0)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven times (three plus zero?)", 
	"Answer" : 21,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-one.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 21,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied seven and three before you added zero.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 + 3 before multiplying 7 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 0 = 3; Now we have 7 X 3 = 21"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 82,
	"Question" : "What is 8 + 7 X 5?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eight plus seven times five?", 
	"Answer" : 43,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-three.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 75,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added eight and seven before you multiplied by five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 7 X 5 before adding 8 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 X 5 = 35; Now we have 8 + 35 = 43"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 83,
	"Question" : "What is (9 + 0) X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (nine plus zero) times three?", 
	"Answer" : 27,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-seven.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 9,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied zero and three before you added nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 9 + 0 before multiplying 3 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 + 0 = 9; Now we have 9 X 3 = 27"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 84,
	"Question" : "What is 6 + 6 X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is six plus six times three?", 
	"Answer" : 24,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 36,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added six and six before you multiplied by three.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 X 3 before adding 6 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 3 = 18; Now we have 6 + 18 = 24"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 85,
	"Question" : "What is 9 X (9 + 7)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine times (nine plus seven?)", 
	"Answer" : 144,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and forty-four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 88,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied nine and nine before you added seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 7 + 9 before multiplying 9 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 + 7 = 16; Now we have 9 X 16 = 144"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 86,
	"Question" : "What is 4 + 2 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four plus two times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 4,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 0,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added four and two before you multiplied by zero.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 2 X 0 before adding 4 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 X 0 = 0; Now we have 4 + 0 = 4"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 87,
	"Question" : "What is (3 + 8) X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (three plus eight) times one?", 
	"Answer" : 11,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eleven.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 11,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied eight and one before you added three.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 3 + 8 before multiplying 1 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 8 = 11; Now we have 11 X 1 = 11"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 88,
	"Question" : "What is 5 + 3 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five plus three times four?", 
	"Answer" : 17,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventeen.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 32,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added five and three before you multiplied by four.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 3 X 4 before adding 5 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 X 4 = 12; Now we have 5 + 12 = 17"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 89,
	"Question" : "What is 7 X (3 + 5)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven times (three plus five?)", 
	"Answer" : 56,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-six.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 26,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied seven and three before you added five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 5 + 3 before multiplying 7 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 5 = 8; Now we have 7 X 8 = 56"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 90,
	"Question" : "What is 6 + 5 X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is six plus five times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 51,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-one.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 99,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added six and five before you multiplied by nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 5 X 9 before adding 6 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 X 9 = 45; Now we have 6 + 45 = 51"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 91,
	"Question" : "What is (7 + 2) X 8?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (seven plus two) times eight?", 
	"Answer" : 72,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventy-two.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 23,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied two and eight before you added seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 7 + 2 before multiplying 8 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 + 2 = 9; Now we have 9 X 8 = 72"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 92,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 0 X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus zero times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 1,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 9,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added one and zero before you multiplied by nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 0 X 9 before adding 1 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 X 9 = 0; Now we have 1 + 0 = 1"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 93,
	"Question" : "What is (2 + 2) X 8?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (two plus two) times eight?", 
	"Answer" : 32,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-two.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 18,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied two and eight before you added two.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 + 2 before multiplying 8 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 + 2 = 4; Now we have 4 X 8 = 32"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 94,
	"Question" : "What is 3 + 1 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three plus one times four?", 
	"Answer" : 7,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seven.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 16,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added three and one before you multiplied by four.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 1 X 4 before adding 3 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 X 4 = 4; Now we have 3 + 4 = 7"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 95,
	"Question" : "What is (2 + 2) X 6?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (two plus two) times six?", 
	"Answer" : 24,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 14,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied two and six before you added two.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 + 2 before multiplying 6 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 + 2 = 4; Now we have 4 X 6 = 24"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 96,
	"Question" : "What is 3 + 1 X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three plus one times three?", 
	"Answer" : 6,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is six.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 12,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added three and one before you multiplied by three.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 1 X 3 before adding 3 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 X 3 = 3; Now we have 3 + 3 = 6"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 97,
	"Question" : "What is 2 X (5 + 8)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is two times (five plus eight?)", 
	"Answer" : 26,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-six.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 18,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied two and five before you added eight.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 8 + 5 before multiplying 2 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 + 8 = 13; Now we have 2 X 13 = 26"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 98,
	"Question" : "What is 9 + 6 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine plus six times two?", 
	"Answer" : 21,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-one.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 30,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added nine and six before you multiplied by two.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 X 2 before adding 9 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 2 = 12; Now we have 9 + 12 = 21"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 99,
	"Question" : "What is 9 X (3 + 1)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine times (three plus one?)", 
	"Answer" : 36,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-six.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 28,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied nine and three before you added one.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 1 + 3 before multiplying 9 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 1 = 4; Now we have 9 X 4 = 36"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 100,
	"Question" : "What is 7 + 1 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven plus one times two?", 
	"Answer" : 9,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is nine.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 16,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added seven and one before you multiplied by two.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 1 X 2 before adding 7 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 X 2 = 2; Now we have 7 + 2 = 9"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 101,
	"Question" : "What is 3 X (1 + 9)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three times (one plus nine?)", 
	"Answer" : 30,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 12,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied three and one before you added nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 9 + 1 before multiplying 3 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 9 = 10; Now we have 3 X 10 = 30"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 102,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 3 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus three times one?", 
	"Answer" : 4,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 4,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added one and three before you multiplied by one.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 3 X 1 before adding 1 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 X 1 = 3; Now we have 1 + 3 = 4"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 103,
	"Question" : "What is 7 X (3 + 0)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven times (three plus zero?)", 
	"Answer" : 21,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-one.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 21,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied seven and three before you added zero.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 + 3 before multiplying 7 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 0 = 3; Now we have 7 X 3 = 21"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 104,
	"Question" : "What is 9 + 8 X 8?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine plus eight times eight?", 
	"Answer" : 73,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventy-three.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 136,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added nine and eight before you multiplied by eight.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 8 X 8 before adding 9 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 X 8 = 64; Now we have 9 + 64 = 73"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 105,
	"Question" : "What is (4 + 8) X 8?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (four plus eight) times eight?", 
	"Answer" : 96,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is ninety-six.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 68,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied eight and eight before you added four.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 4 + 8 before multiplying 8 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "4 + 8 = 12; Now we have 12 X 8 = 96"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 106,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 6 X 6?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus six times six?", 
	"Answer" : 37,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-seven.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 42,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added one and six before you multiplied by six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 X 6 before adding 1 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 6 = 36; Now we have 1 + 36 = 37"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 107,
	"Question" : "What is 5 X (1 + 2)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five times (one plus two?)", 
	"Answer" : 15,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifteen.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 7,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied five and one before you added two.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 + 1 before multiplying 5 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 2 = 3; Now we have 5 X 3 = 15"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 108,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 0 X 7?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus zero times seven?", 
	"Answer" : 1,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 7,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added one and zero before you multiplied by seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 0 X 7 before adding 1 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 X 7 = 0; Now we have 1 + 0 = 1"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 109,
	"Question" : "What is (4 + 2) X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (four plus two) times one?", 
	"Answer" : 6,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is six.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 6,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied two and one before you added four.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 4 + 2 before multiplying 1 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "4 + 2 = 6; Now we have 6 X 1 = 6"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 110,
	"Question" : "What is 4 + 6 X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four plus six times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 58,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-eight.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 90,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added four and six before you multiplied by nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 X 9 before adding 4 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 9 = 54; Now we have 4 + 54 = 58"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 111,
	"Question" : "What is (8 + 8) X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (eight plus eight) times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 0,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is zero.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 8,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied eight and zero before you added eight.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 8 + 8 before multiplying 0 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 + 8 = 16; Now we have 16 X 0 = 0"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 112,
	"Question" : "What is 7 + 3 X 8?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven plus three times eight?", 
	"Answer" : 31,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-one.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 80,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added seven and three before you multiplied by eight.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 3 X 8 before adding 7 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 X 8 = 24; Now we have 7 + 24 = 31"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 113,
	"Question" : "What is 6 X (9 + 5)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is six times (nine plus five?)", 
	"Answer" : 84,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eighty-four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 59,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied six and nine before you added five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 5 + 9 before multiplying 6 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 + 5 = 14; Now we have 6 X 14 = 84"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 114,
	"Question" : "What is 2 + 5 X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is two plus five times three?", 
	"Answer" : 17,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventeen.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 21,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added two and five before you multiplied by three.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 5 X 3 before adding 2 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 X 3 = 15; Now we have 2 + 15 = 17"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 115,
	"Question" : "What is 1 X (1 + 3)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one times (one plus three?)", 
	"Answer" : 4,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 4,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied one and one before you added three.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 3 + 1 before multiplying 1 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 3 = 4; Now we have 1 X 4 = 4"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 116,
	"Question" : "What is 2 + 2 X 5?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is two plus two times five?", 
	"Answer" : 12,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twelve.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 20,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added two and two before you multiplied by five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 2 X 5 before adding 2 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 X 5 = 10; Now we have 2 + 10 = 12"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 117,
	"Question" : "What is 4 X (9 + 1)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four times (nine plus one?)", 
	"Answer" : 40,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 37,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied four and nine before you added one.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 1 + 9 before multiplying 4 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 + 1 = 10; Now we have 4 X 10 = 40"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 118,
	"Question" : "What is 9 + 7 X 5?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine plus seven times five?", 
	"Answer" : 44,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 80,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added nine and seven before you multiplied by five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 7 X 5 before adding 9 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 X 5 = 35; Now we have 9 + 35 = 44"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 119,
	"Question" : "What is 8 X (9 + 9)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eight times (nine plus nine?)", 
	"Answer" : 144,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and forty-four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 81,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied eight and nine before you added nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 9 + 9 before multiplying 8 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 + 9 = 18; Now we have 8 X 18 = 144"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 120,
	"Question" : "What is 4 + 2 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four plus two times two?", 
	"Answer" : 8,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eight.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 12,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added four and two before you multiplied by two.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 2 X 2 before adding 4 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 X 2 = 4; Now we have 4 + 4 = 8"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 121,
	"Question" : "What is 9 X (3 + 9)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine times (three plus nine?)", 
	"Answer" : 108,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and eight.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 36,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied nine and three before you added nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 9 + 3 before multiplying 9 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 9 = 12; Now we have 9 X 12 = 108"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 122,
	"Question" : "What is 5 + 6 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five plus six times two?", 
	"Answer" : 17,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventeen.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 22,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added five and six before you multiplied by two.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 X 2 before adding 5 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 2 = 12; Now we have 5 + 12 = 17"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 123,
	"Question" : "What is (2 + 8) X 8?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (two plus eight) times eight?", 
	"Answer" : 80,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eighty.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 66,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied eight and eight before you added two.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 + 8 before multiplying 8 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 + 8 = 10; Now we have 10 X 8 = 80"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 124,
	"Question" : "What is 7 + 1 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven plus one times one?", 
	"Answer" : 8,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eight.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 8,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added seven and one before you multiplied by one.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 1 X 1 before adding 7 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 X 1 = 1; Now we have 7 + 1 = 8"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 125,
	"Question" : "What is 4 X (3 + 2)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four times (three plus two?)", 
	"Answer" : 20,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 14,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied four and three before you added two.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 + 3 before multiplying 4 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 2 = 5; Now we have 4 X 5 = 20"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 126,
	"Question" : "What is 5 + 6 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five plus six times two?", 
	"Answer" : 17,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventeen.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 22,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added five and six before you multiplied by two.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 X 2 before adding 5 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 2 = 12; Now we have 5 + 12 = 17"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 127,
	"Question" : "What is (7 + 4) X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (seven plus four) times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 0,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is zero.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 7,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied four and zero before you added seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 7 + 4 before multiplying 0 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 + 4 = 11; Now we have 11 X 0 = 0"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 128,
	"Question" : "What is 4 + 0 X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four plus zero times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 4,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 36,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added four and zero before you multiplied by nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 0 X 9 before adding 4 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 X 9 = 0; Now we have 4 + 0 = 4"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 129,
	"Question" : "What is (5 + 8) X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (five plus eight) times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 0,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is zero.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 5,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied eight and zero before you added five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 5 + 8 before multiplying 0 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 + 8 = 13; Now we have 13 X 0 = 0"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 130,
	"Question" : "What is 9 + 2 X 8?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine plus two times eight?", 
	"Answer" : 25,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-five.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 88,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added nine and two before you multiplied by eight.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 2 X 8 before adding 9 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 X 8 = 16; Now we have 9 + 16 = 25"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 131,
	"Question" : "What is (3 + 0) X 8?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (three plus zero) times eight?", 
	"Answer" : 24,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 3,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied zero and eight before you added three.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 3 + 0 before multiplying 8 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 0 = 3; Now we have 3 X 8 = 24"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 132,
	"Question" : "What is 8 + 0 X 7?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eight plus zero times seven?", 
	"Answer" : 8,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eight.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 56,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added eight and zero before you multiplied by seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 0 X 7 before adding 8 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 X 7 = 0; Now we have 8 + 0 = 8"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 133,
	"Question" : "What is 3 X (3 + 7)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three times (three plus seven?)", 
	"Answer" : 30,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 16,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied three and three before you added seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 7 + 3 before multiplying 3 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 7 = 10; Now we have 3 X 10 = 30"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 134,
	"Question" : "What is 8 + 2 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eight plus two times two?", 
	"Answer" : 12,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twelve.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 20,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added eight and two before you multiplied by two.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 2 X 2 before adding 8 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 X 2 = 4; Now we have 8 + 4 = 12"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 135,
	"Question" : "What is 5 X (9 + 2)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five times (nine plus two?)", 
	"Answer" : 55,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-five.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 47,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied five and nine before you added two.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 + 9 before multiplying 5 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 + 2 = 11; Now we have 5 X 11 = 55"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 136,
	"Question" : "What is 5 + 3 X 5?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five plus three times five?", 
	"Answer" : 20,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 40,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added five and three before you multiplied by five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 3 X 5 before adding 5 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 X 5 = 15; Now we have 5 + 15 = 20"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 137,
	"Question" : "What is (4 + 2) X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (four plus two) times four?", 
	"Answer" : 24,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 12,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied two and four before you added four.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 4 + 2 before multiplying 4 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "4 + 2 = 6; Now we have 6 X 4 = 24"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 138,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 6 X 7?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus six times seven?", 
	"Answer" : 43,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-three.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 49,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added one and six before you multiplied by seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 X 7 before adding 1 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 7 = 42; Now we have 1 + 42 = 43"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 139,
	"Question" : "What is (8 + 6) X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (eight plus six) times three?", 
	"Answer" : 42,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-two.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 26,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied six and three before you added eight.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 8 + 6 before multiplying 3 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 + 6 = 14; Now we have 14 X 3 = 42"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 140,
	"Question" : "What is 4 + 4 X 5?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four plus four times five?", 
	"Answer" : 24,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 40,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added four and four before you multiplied by five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 4 X 5 before adding 4 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "4 X 5 = 20; Now we have 4 + 20 = 24"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 141,
	"Question" : "What is 3 X (5 + 5)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three times (five plus five?)", 
	"Answer" : 30,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 20,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied three and five before you added five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 5 + 5 before multiplying 3 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 + 5 = 10; Now we have 3 X 10 = 30"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 142,
	"Question" : "What is 2 + 4 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is two plus four times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 2,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is two.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 0,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added two and four before you multiplied by zero.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 4 X 0 before adding 2 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "4 X 0 = 0; Now we have 2 + 0 = 2"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 143,
	"Question" : "What is (9 + 0) X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (nine plus zero) times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 81,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eighty-one.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 9,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied zero and nine before you added nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 9 + 0 before multiplying 9 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 + 0 = 9; Now we have 9 X 9 = 81"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 144,
	"Question" : "What is 6 + 7 X 7?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is six plus seven times seven?", 
	"Answer" : 55,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-five.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 91,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added six and seven before you multiplied by seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 7 X 7 before adding 6 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 X 7 = 49; Now we have 6 + 49 = 55"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 145,
	"Question" : "What is 9 X (7 + 1)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine times (seven plus one?)", 
	"Answer" : 72,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventy-two.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 64,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied nine and seven before you added one.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 1 + 7 before multiplying 9 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 + 1 = 8; Now we have 9 X 8 = 72"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 146,
	"Question" : "What is 6 + 6 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is six plus six times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 6,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is six.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 0,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added six and six before you multiplied by zero.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 X 0 before adding 6 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 0 = 0; Now we have 6 + 0 = 6"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 147,
	"Question" : "What is 1 X (3 + 0)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one times (three plus zero?)", 
	"Answer" : 3,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is three.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 3,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied one and three before you added zero.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 + 3 before multiplying 1 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 0 = 3; Now we have 1 X 3 = 3"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 148,
	"Question" : "What is 8 + 1 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eight plus one times one?", 
	"Answer" : 9,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is nine.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 9,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added eight and one before you multiplied by one.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 1 X 1 before adding 8 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 X 1 = 1; Now we have 8 + 1 = 9"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 149,
	"Question" : "What is 7 X (9 + 7)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven times (nine plus seven?)", 
	"Answer" : 112,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and twelve.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 70,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied seven and nine before you added seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 7 + 9 before multiplying 7 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 + 7 = 16; Now we have 7 X 16 = 112"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 150,
	"Question" : "What is 5 + 4 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five plus four times one?", 
	"Answer" : 9,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is nine.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 9,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added five and four before you multiplied by one.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 4 X 1 before adding 5 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "4 X 1 = 4; Now we have 5 + 4 = 9"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 151,
	"Question" : "What is 2 X (7 + 7)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is two times (seven plus seven?)", 
	"Answer" : 28,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-eight.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 21,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied two and seven before you added seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 7 + 7 before multiplying 2 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 + 7 = 14; Now we have 2 X 14 = 28"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 152,
	"Question" : "What is 7 + 9 X 7?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven plus nine times seven?", 
	"Answer" : 70,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventy.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 112,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added seven and nine before you multiplied by seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 9 X 7 before adding 7 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 X 7 = 63; Now we have 7 + 63 = 70"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 153,
	"Question" : "What is 3 X (3 + 8)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three times (three plus eight?)", 
	"Answer" : 33,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-three.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 17,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied three and three before you added eight.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 8 + 3 before multiplying 3 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 8 = 11; Now we have 3 X 11 = 33"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 154,
	"Question" : "What is 3 + 3 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three plus three times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 3,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is three.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 0,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added three and three before you multiplied by zero.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 3 X 0 before adding 3 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 X 0 = 0; Now we have 3 + 0 = 3"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 155,
	"Question" : "What is 8 X (9 + 6)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eight times (nine plus six?)", 
	"Answer" : 120,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and twenty.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 78,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied eight and nine before you added six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 6 + 9 before multiplying 8 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 + 6 = 15; Now we have 8 X 15 = 120"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 156,
	"Question" : "What is 7 + 6 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven plus six times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 7,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seven.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 0,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added seven and six before you multiplied by zero.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 X 0 before adding 7 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 0 = 0; Now we have 7 + 0 = 7"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 157,
	"Question" : "What is 8 X (7 + 5)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eight times (seven plus five?)", 
	"Answer" : 96,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is ninety-six.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 61,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied eight and seven before you added five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 5 + 7 before multiplying 8 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 + 5 = 12; Now we have 8 X 12 = 96"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 158,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 4 X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus four times three?", 
	"Answer" : 13,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirteen.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 15,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added one and four before you multiplied by three.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 4 X 3 before adding 1 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "4 X 3 = 12; Now we have 1 + 12 = 13"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 159,
	"Question" : "What is 5 X (3 + 7)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five times (three plus seven?)", 
	"Answer" : 50,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 22,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied five and three before you added seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 7 + 3 before multiplying 5 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 7 = 10; Now we have 5 X 10 = 50"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 160,
	"Question" : "What is 2 + 4 X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is two plus four times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 38,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-eight.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 54,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added two and four before you multiplied by nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 4 X 9 before adding 2 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "4 X 9 = 36; Now we have 2 + 36 = 38"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 161,
	"Question" : "What is 7 X (7 + 2)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven times (seven plus two?)", 
	"Answer" : 63,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixty-three.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 51,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied seven and seven before you added two.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 + 7 before multiplying 7 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 + 2 = 9; Now we have 7 X 9 = 63"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 162,
	"Question" : "What is 5 + 3 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five plus three times one?", 
	"Answer" : 8,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eight.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 8,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added five and three before you multiplied by one.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 3 X 1 before adding 5 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 X 1 = 3; Now we have 5 + 3 = 8"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 163,
	"Question" : "What is (2 + 4) X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (two plus four) times one?", 
	"Answer" : 6,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is six.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 6,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied four and one before you added two.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 + 4 before multiplying 1 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 + 4 = 6; Now we have 6 X 1 = 6"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 164,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 6 X 7?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus six times seven?", 
	"Answer" : 43,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-three.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 49,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added one and six before you multiplied by seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 X 7 before adding 1 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 7 = 42; Now we have 1 + 42 = 43"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 165,
	"Question" : "What is 5 X (3 + 8)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five times (three plus eight?)", 
	"Answer" : 55,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-five.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 23,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied five and three before you added eight.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 8 + 3 before multiplying 5 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 8 = 11; Now we have 5 X 11 = 55"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 166,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 0 X 8?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus zero times eight?", 
	"Answer" : 1,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 8,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added one and zero before you multiplied by eight.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 0 X 8 before adding 1 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 X 8 = 0; Now we have 1 + 0 = 1"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 167,
	"Question" : "What is 3 X (7 + 5)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three times (seven plus five?)", 
	"Answer" : 36,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-six.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 26,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied three and seven before you added five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 5 + 7 before multiplying 3 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 + 5 = 12; Now we have 3 X 12 = 36"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 168,
	"Question" : "What is 7 + 4 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven plus four times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 7,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seven.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 0,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added seven and four before you multiplied by zero.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 4 X 0 before adding 7 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "4 X 0 = 0; Now we have 7 + 0 = 7"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 169,
	"Question" : "What is 5 X (5 + 6)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five times (five plus six?)", 
	"Answer" : 55,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-five.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 31,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied five and five before you added six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 6 + 5 before multiplying 5 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 + 6 = 11; Now we have 5 X 11 = 55"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 170,
	"Question" : "What is 5 + 2 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five plus two times two?", 
	"Answer" : 9,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is nine.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 14,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added five and two before you multiplied by two.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 2 X 2 before adding 5 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 X 2 = 4; Now we have 5 + 4 = 9"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 171,
	"Question" : "What is 6 X (1 + 7)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is six times (one plus seven?)", 
	"Answer" : 48,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-eight.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 13,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied six and one before you added seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 7 + 1 before multiplying 6 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 7 = 8; Now we have 6 X 8 = 48"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 172,
	"Question" : "What is 4 + 5 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four plus five times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 4,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 0,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added four and five before you multiplied by zero.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 5 X 0 before adding 4 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 X 0 = 0; Now we have 4 + 0 = 4"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 173,
	"Question" : "What is 7 X (7 + 9)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven times (seven plus nine?)", 
	"Answer" : 112,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and twelve.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 58,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied seven and seven before you added nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 9 + 7 before multiplying 7 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 + 9 = 16; Now we have 7 X 16 = 112"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 174,
	"Question" : "What is 5 + 1 X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five plus one times three?", 
	"Answer" : 8,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eight.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 18,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added five and one before you multiplied by three.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 1 X 3 before adding 5 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 X 3 = 3; Now we have 5 + 3 = 8"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 175,
	"Question" : "What is 3 X (5 + 4)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three times (five plus four?)", 
	"Answer" : 27,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-seven.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 19,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied three and five before you added four.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 4 + 5 before multiplying 3 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 + 4 = 9; Now we have 3 X 9 = 27"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 176,
	"Question" : "What is 3 + 7 X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three plus seven times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 66,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixty-six.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 90,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added three and seven before you multiplied by nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 7 X 9 before adding 3 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 X 9 = 63; Now we have 3 + 63 = 66"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 177,
	"Question" : "What is 2 X (3 + 3)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is two times (three plus three?)", 
	"Answer" : 12,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twelve.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 9,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied two and three before you added three.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 3 + 3 before multiplying 2 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 3 = 6; Now we have 2 X 6 = 12"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 178,
	"Question" : "What is 7 + 1 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven plus one times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 7,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seven.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 0,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added seven and one before you multiplied by zero.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 1 X 0 before adding 7 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 X 0 = 0; Now we have 7 + 0 = 7"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 179,
	"Question" : "What is 7 X (1 + 9)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven times (one plus nine?)", 
	"Answer" : 70,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventy.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 16,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied seven and one before you added nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 9 + 1 before multiplying 7 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 9 = 10; Now we have 7 X 10 = 70"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 180,
	"Question" : "What is 2 + 4 X 5?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is two plus four times five?", 
	"Answer" : 22,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-two.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 30,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added two and four before you multiplied by five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 4 X 5 before adding 2 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "4 X 5 = 20; Now we have 2 + 20 = 22"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 181,
	"Question" : "What is 4 X (9 + 5)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four times (nine plus five?)", 
	"Answer" : 56,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-six.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 41,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied four and nine before you added five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 5 + 9 before multiplying 4 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 + 5 = 14; Now we have 4 X 14 = 56"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 182,
	"Question" : "What is 5 + 6 X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five plus six times three?", 
	"Answer" : 23,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-three.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 33,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added five and six before you multiplied by three.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 X 3 before adding 5 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 3 = 18; Now we have 5 + 18 = 23"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 183,
	"Question" : "What is 5 X (3 + 5)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five times (three plus five?)", 
	"Answer" : 40,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 20,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied five and three before you added five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 5 + 3 before multiplying 5 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 5 = 8; Now we have 5 X 8 = 40"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 184,
	"Question" : "What is 6 + 5 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is six plus five times two?", 
	"Answer" : 16,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixteen.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 22,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added six and five before you multiplied by two.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 5 X 2 before adding 6 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 X 2 = 10; Now we have 6 + 10 = 16"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 185,
	"Question" : "What is (7 + 8) X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (seven plus eight) times four?", 
	"Answer" : 60,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixty.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 39,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied eight and four before you added seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 7 + 8 before multiplying 4 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 + 8 = 15; Now we have 15 X 4 = 60"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 186,
	"Question" : "What is 4 + 9 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four plus nine times two?", 
	"Answer" : 22,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-two.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 26,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added four and nine before you multiplied by two.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 9 X 2 before adding 4 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 X 2 = 18; Now we have 4 + 18 = 22"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 187,
	"Question" : "What is 6 X (7 + 7)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is six times (seven plus seven?)", 
	"Answer" : 84,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eighty-four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 49,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied six and seven before you added seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 7 + 7 before multiplying 6 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 + 7 = 14; Now we have 6 X 14 = 84"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 188,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 8 X 6?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus eight times six?", 
	"Answer" : 49,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-nine.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 54,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added one and eight before you multiplied by six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 8 X 6 before adding 1 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 X 6 = 48; Now we have 1 + 48 = 49"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 189,
	"Question" : "What is (5 + 8) X 5?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (five plus eight) times five?", 
	"Answer" : 65,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixty-five.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 45,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied eight and five before you added five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 5 + 8 before multiplying 5 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 + 8 = 13; Now we have 13 X 5 = 65"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 190,
	"Question" : "What is 6 + 6 X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is six plus six times three?", 
	"Answer" : 24,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 36,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added six and six before you multiplied by three.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 X 3 before adding 6 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 3 = 18; Now we have 6 + 18 = 24"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 191,
	"Question" : "What is 6 X (7 + 1)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is six times (seven plus one?)", 
	"Answer" : 48,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-eight.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 43,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied six and seven before you added one.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 1 + 7 before multiplying 6 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 + 1 = 8; Now we have 6 X 8 = 48"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 192,
	"Question" : "What is 3 + 3 X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three plus three times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 30,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 54,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added three and three before you multiplied by nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 3 X 9 before adding 3 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 X 9 = 27; Now we have 3 + 27 = 30"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 193,
	"Question" : "What is 2 X (5 + 9)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is two times (five plus nine?)", 
	"Answer" : 28,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-eight.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 19,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied two and five before you added nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 9 + 5 before multiplying 2 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 + 9 = 14; Now we have 2 X 14 = 28"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 194,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 9 X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus nine times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 82,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eighty-two.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 90,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added one and nine before you multiplied by nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 9 X 9 before adding 1 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 X 9 = 81; Now we have 1 + 81 = 82"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 195,
	"Question" : "What is (6 + 4) X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (six plus four) times two?", 
	"Answer" : 20,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 14,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied four and two before you added six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 6 + 4 before multiplying 2 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 + 4 = 10; Now we have 10 X 2 = 20"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 196,
	"Question" : "What is 8 + 2 X 6?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eight plus two times six?", 
	"Answer" : 20,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 60,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added eight and two before you multiplied by six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 2 X 6 before adding 8 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 X 6 = 12; Now we have 8 + 12 = 20"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 197,
	"Question" : "What is 7 X (9 + 6)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven times (nine plus six?)", 
	"Answer" : 105,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and five.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 69,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied seven and nine before you added six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 6 + 9 before multiplying 7 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 + 6 = 15; Now we have 7 X 15 = 105"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 198,
	"Question" : "What is 3 + 9 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three plus nine times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 3,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is three.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 0,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added three and nine before you multiplied by zero.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 9 X 0 before adding 3 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 X 0 = 0; Now we have 3 + 0 = 3"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 199,
	"Question" : "What is 4 X (3 + 0)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four times (three plus zero?)", 
	"Answer" : 12,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twelve.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 12,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied four and three before you added zero.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 + 3 before multiplying 4 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 0 = 3; Now we have 4 X 3 = 12"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 200,
	"Question" : "What is 9 + 6 X 6?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine plus six times six?", 
	"Answer" : 45,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-five.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 90,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added nine and six before you multiplied by six.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 X 6 before adding 9 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 6 = 36; Now we have 9 + 36 = 45"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 201,
	"Question" : "What is (3 + 4) X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (three plus four) times three?", 
	"Answer" : 21,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-one.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 15,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied four and three before you added three.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 3 + 4 before multiplying 3 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 4 = 7; Now we have 7 X 3 = 21"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 202,
	"Question" : "What is 9 + 8 X 5?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine plus eight times five?", 
	"Answer" : 49,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-nine.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 85,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added nine and eight before you multiplied by five.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 8 X 5 before adding 9 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 X 5 = 40; Now we have 9 + 40 = 49"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 203,
	"Question" : "What is (3 + 0) X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (three plus zero) times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 0,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is zero.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 3,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied zero and zero before you added three.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 3 + 0 before multiplying 0 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 0 = 3; Now we have 3 X 0 = 0"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 204,
	"Question" : "What is 8 + 9 X 8?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eight plus nine times eight?", 
	"Answer" : 80,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eighty.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 136,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added eight and nine before you multiplied by eight.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 9 X 8 before adding 8 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 X 8 = 72; Now we have 8 + 72 = 80"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 205,
	"Question" : "What is 7 X (9 + 2)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven times (nine plus two?)", 
	"Answer" : 77,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventy-seven.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 65,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied seven and nine before you added two.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 + 9 before multiplying 7 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 + 2 = 11; Now we have 7 X 11 = 77"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 206,
	"Question" : "What is 3 + 2 X 7?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three plus two times seven?", 
	"Answer" : 17,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventeen.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 35,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added three and two before you multiplied by seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 2 X 7 before adding 3 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 X 7 = 14; Now we have 3 + 14 = 17"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 207,
	"Question" : "What is (9 + 4) X 7?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (nine plus four) times seven?", 
	"Answer" : 91,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is ninety-one.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 37,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied four and seven before you added nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 9 + 4 before multiplying 7 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 + 4 = 13; Now we have 13 X 7 = 91"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 208,
	"Question" : "What is 6 + 4 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is six plus four times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 6,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is six.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 0,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added six and four before you multiplied by zero.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 4 X 0 before adding 6 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "4 X 0 = 0; Now we have 6 + 0 = 6"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 209,
	"Question" : "What is 2 X (9 + 4)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is two times (nine plus four?)", 
	"Answer" : 26,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-six.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 22,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied two and nine before you added four.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 4 + 9 before multiplying 2 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 + 4 = 13; Now we have 2 X 13 = 26"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 210,
	"Question" : "What is 7 + 3 X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven plus three times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 34,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 90,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added seven and three before you multiplied by nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 3 X 9 before adding 7 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 X 9 = 27; Now we have 7 + 27 = 34"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 211,
	"Question" : "What is (1 + 2) X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (one plus two) times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 27,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-seven.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 19,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied two and nine before you added one.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 1 + 2 before multiplying 9 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 2 = 3; Now we have 3 X 9 = 27"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 212,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 6 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus six times four?", 
	"Answer" : 25,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-five.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 28,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added one and six before you multiplied by four.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 X 4 before adding 1 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 4 = 24; Now we have 1 + 24 = 25"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 213,
	"Question" : "What is (8 + 2) X 8?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (eight plus two) times eight?", 
	"Answer" : 80,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eighty.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 24,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied two and eight before you added eight.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 8 + 2 before multiplying 8 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 + 2 = 10; Now we have 10 X 8 = 80"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 214,
	"Question" : "What is 8 + 4 X 9?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eight plus four times nine?", 
	"Answer" : 44,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 108,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added eight and four before you multiplied by nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 4 X 9 before adding 8 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "4 X 9 = 36; Now we have 8 + 36 = 44"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 215,
	"Question" : "What is 9 X (9 + 9)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine times (nine plus nine?)", 
	"Answer" : 162,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and sixty-two.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 90,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied nine and nine before you added nine.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 9 + 9 before multiplying 9 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 + 9 = 18; Now we have 9 X 18 = 162"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 216,
	"Question" : "What is 4 + 2 X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four plus two times three?", 
	"Answer" : 10,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is ten.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 18,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added four and two before you multiplied by three.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 2 X 3 before adding 4 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 X 3 = 6; Now we have 4 + 6 = 10"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 217,
	"Question" : "What is 3 X (1 + 7)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three times (one plus seven?)", 
	"Answer" : 24,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 10,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied three and one before you added seven.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 7 + 1 before multiplying 3 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 7 = 8; Now we have 3 X 8 = 24"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 218,
	"Question" : "What is 9 + 0 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine plus zero times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 9,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is nine.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 0,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you added nine and zero before you multiplied by zero.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 0 X 0 before adding 9 to that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 X 0 = 0; Now we have 9 + 0 = 9"
	}
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 219,
	"Question" : "What is 9 X (3 + 3)?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine times (three plus three?)", 
	"Answer" : 54,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-four.",
	"Difficulty Level" : 1,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60,
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 30,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : "I think you multiplied nine and three before you added three.",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 3 + 3 before multiplying 9 with that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 3 = 6; Now we have 9 X 6 = 54"
	}
 }
]
